I'm trying to figure out when y'all are going to realize what world we're in.
That's really honestly what I'm trying to figure out.
You're on this app like me.
And even though our algorithms are different, I know that you're seeing what I'm seeing,
even if it's only 20% of what I'm seeing.
And yet, I still see so many of you all pretending that everything is just regular.
And I'm trying to understand what the hell world y'all think you're in.
I'm trying to understand why y'all think 2025 is so far away from 1965.
Like, are you that self-involved?
Are you that self-centered?
Are you that short-sighted?
We still, we finding fossils from millions of years ago and y'all are acting like 1965 was another, like, eon.
Explain it to me.
We're not cooked.
We're dumb.
And when y'all talk about the end times, I really, again, I'm like, you're so self-centered.
You're so self-involved.
It's disgusting to watch.
As someone who's been on this, I've been here before.
To see this version of humans is just irritating.
It's the end times.
Why?
Because you're experiencing some shit that people the world over have experienced over and over and over and over again.
But now it's the end times.
Y'all don't know nothing about nothing.
That's what's so irritating.
Because I got to be here with y'all.
Been going on for centuries.
It just didn't happen to you.
This whole idea about Zoron, well, he's probably getting threats.
This woman was arrested.
Gades.
George Jackson, another brother who was a member of the Panthers and was in prison for a crime he didn't commit.
He's escaping from prison.
We are in Asia burning down the presidential palace.
We're looking at the Congo running up on one of their mayors, running up on his dwelling.
Like, oh, you got a check to sell us out to the M23?
Watch what happens.
We looking at Nepal.
They just burned down their whole shit.
Their whole prime minister's building.
They had to airlift their goddamn congresspeople out.
Well, maybe they were sending Zoron death threats and that's why he's capitulating.
Listen, this is the first time, to be quite honest, this is the first time in U.S. history that I have seen people unwilling to die for liberation.
So, when you talk about we're cooked, you're not.
You're comfortable.
You're worrying about your life in a way that's impractical because at the end of the day, they'll take your life.
This is the first time when y'all say, oh, you know, my ancestors died to vote.
They did not die to vote.
Your ancestors were murdered because they were proving that they should be able to participate as citizens in the country that call them citizens.
It wasn't about, I want to vote.
It was, I want to be seen as a citizen in the nation I built.
And you know what happened when they got the right to vote?
So, the United States immediately began working to reverse it.
And these people have been patient.
And instead, you motherfuckers are sitting here talking about, well, you know, so-and-so got threatened and da-da-da-da-da.
Like, I just, if you want me to stop yelling, get the fuck off of my page.
I'm so tired of you people.
I am so tired of you people.
You basic ass motherfuckers who don't even deserve leaders like myself.
You don't.
I'm just, people love to say, well, we don't leaders.
No.
You don't have no fucking discipline.
Principles.
You don't have no integrity.
That's why you don't have no leaders.
Because you don't have a fucking goal that requires leadership.
It's just, oh, I'm trying to do me.
I'm trying to do me.
I got to take care of me.
I got to take care of my kids.
Y'all love to do that one.
That's the favorite one.
I got to take care of my kids.
As if the world hasn't had kids that have to get taken care of for eternity.
I got, I got to take care of my kids.
I'm so tired of I got to take care of my kids.
As if these motherfuckers didn't have kids this whole goddamn time.
And the wild part is that, yes, you do got to take care of your kids.
And you're doing it alone because nobody, that's not fair.
Because so many of us refuse to realize that we have been trained to distrust each other.
And y'all with the one human race and all this shit, listen, running for office.
Why does there have to be an upside?
This is what I mean by y'all do not understand where we are.
Is there an upside to running for office?
Look at this dumb bitch.
Because when y'all come at me crazy, I'm going to come at you crazy.
Look at this dumb bitch, Ace of Ashes.
Girl, you got some ego.
Nepal is ranked 126 out of 145 in military strength.
U.S. is ranked number one.
It's dishonest to pretend like conditions are the same here.
Or we won't be met with massacre if we tried.
Listen, you fucking idiot.
We will be met with a massacre.
And the fact that you're not willing to die is why you will eventually be met with a massacre.
Yeah.
That's how that's going to go.
So what you're trying to, like this whole, like we're trying to mitigate harm.
We're going to war.
Ben, it's maddening.
It's maddening.
I got a white bitch in here telling me I got an ego.
Like this is what I'm saying.
Like the internet has got y'all so lost.
The internet has got y'all so lost.
I just, I don't, I don't, I don't, I already blocked her.
So, you know, until, don't ask me what the move is.
If you're, if you haven't, Val, am I, listen.
I saw a post today from a woman who was talking about how, you know, Nigeria and Africans are creating tech for problems that folks in the US aren't even acknowledging.
Like they're like, how do we create apps for banking without banks?
How do, how do we create an app that's usable without Wi-Fi?
Like how do we connect, how do we create like a WhatsApp that's usable without Wi-Fi?
How do we create like apps that are useful for impending destruction of infrastructure?
And yet over here, and she talks about this in the, in the, in the, in the post, she says, but over here in the US, they talk about giving funding to an app that tells you when you need to drink some water.
No, Soursop, Soursop, I like the taste of Soursop, but it like, it actually messes up my throat.
So, I just wanted to give you all something to think about before you go to bed.
There is no reason to think that we are in a state of, um, regularity.
We are not.
We are in a state that many other nations have been in.
And, um, I'm gonna go have some tea.
And no, I do not have an email.
What'd you contact me on?
What'd you contact me to talk about?
This is La Mumba.
That's who this is.
La Mumba.
Right, Bubbles?
You all have a good night.
And, um, I want you to really say to yourself, am I keeping it a buck with myself?
Am I really, like, being honest?
Yes, Patrice.
Well, Pawtree, La Mumba.
Am I really being honest with the world I'm in?
Lando passed away.
Because I don't think y'all are.
Jordi, what's up?
What's up?
Come here.
You're jealous?
Yeah, you're jealous.
Say hi to them.
Say hi to the people.
Tomorrow morning, views for Amanda Land, 10 a.m. Eastern, YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
I'll see you there.
It is time for bed.
Tomorrow morning, 10 a.m. Eastern, YouTube, Amanda Seals TV.
Someone said our country is still in its infancy.
Baby, this country is a rat.
Don't you know some infants don't even make it out of infancy?